<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<plugins>
    <plugin id="com.cd.comment_generator"
        url="https://github.com/cdcountrydelight/Plugin-Manager/raw/refs/heads/master/comment_generator-1.0.1.zip"
        version="1.0.1">
        <idea-version since-build="241" />
        <name>Comment Generator</name>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><strong>This plugin adds a convenient 'Generate Comment' action</strong> to the context menu when right-clicking on a file. Upon selecting the action, it automatically generates and adds documentation comments to methods and functions in the file by calling the Gemini API.</p>
            <p>For the first-time setup, users will be prompted to enter their API key, which can be stored and later updated through the plugin’s settings page.</p>
            <p><strong>Key Benefits:</strong></p>
            <ul>
                <li>Automatically generates Javadoc-style comments for methods and functions in your code.</li>
                <li>Prompted for an API key upon first use, with easy API key management through the settings page.</li>
                <li>Simplifies the process of adding documentation, improving code readability and maintainability.</li>
            </ul>
            <p>This plugin streamlines the process of adding documentation to your code with minimal effort.</p>]]>
        </description>
        <category>Code tools</category>
        <tags>comment, documentation, javadoc, kdoc, kotlin, java, gemini</tags>
        <depends>com.intellij.modules.java</depends>
        <depends>org.jetbrains.kotlin</depends>
        <change-notes>
            <ol>
                <li>
                    <b>Introduced a dedicated icon</b>
                    for the <b>Generate Comment</b> action, enhancing visual clarity.
                </li>
                <li>
                    <b>Improved regex logic</b>
                    for more accurate comment extraction and parsing.
                </li>
                <li>
                    <b>Upgraded Gemini integration</b>
                    to the latest supported version for better performance.
                </li>
                <li>
                    <b>Added compatibility with Kotlin K2 mode</b>
                    , enabling support for the latest Kotlin analysis API.
                </li>
                <li>
                    <b>Refactored package structure</b>
                    for improved maintainability and scalability of the plugin.
                </li>
                <li>
                    <b>Enhanced comment generation logic</b>
                    to intelligently produce both Javadoc and KDoc based on file type.
                </li>
            </ol>
        </change-notes>
        <vendor email="info@countrydelight.in" url="https://countrydelight.in/">Country Delight
        </vendor>
    </plugin>
    <!--    <plugin id="com.cd.test_cases_generator"-->
    <!--        url="https://github.com/cdcountrydelight/Plugin-Manager/blob/master/test_cases_generator-1.0.1.jar"-->
    <!--        version="1.0.1">-->
    <!--        <idea-version since-build="241" />-->
    <!--        <name>Test Cases Generator</name>-->
    <!--    </plugin>-->
    <!--    <plugin id="com.cd.ClassDiagramGenerator"-->
    <!--        url="https://github.com/cdcountrydelight/Plugin-Manager/blob/master/ClassDiagramGenerator-1.0.4.jar"-->
    <!--        version="1.0.4">-->
    <!--        <idea-version since-build="241" />-->
    <!--        <name>Test Cases Generator</name>-->
    <!--    </plugin>-->
</plugins>