<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<plugins>
    <!--  comment generator -->
    <plugin id="com.cd.comment_generator"
        url="https://github.com/cdcountrydelight/Plugin-Manager/raw/refs/heads/master/comment_generator-1.0.5.zip"
        version="1.0.5">
        <idea-version since-build="241" until-build="251.*" />
        <name>Comment Generator</name>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
                <p><strong>This plugin adds a convenient 'Generate Comment' action</strong> to the context menu when right-clicking on a file. Upon selecting the action, it automatically generates and adds documentation comments to methods and functions in the file by calling the Gemini API.</p>
                <p>For the first-time setup, users will be prompted to enter their API key, which can be stored and later updated through the plugin’s settings page.</p>
                <p><strong>Key Benefits:</strong></p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Automatically generates Javadoc-style comments for methods and functions in your code.</li>
                    <li>Prompted for an API key upon first use, with easy API key management through the settings page.</li>
                    <li>Simplifies the process of adding documentation, improving code readability and maintainability.</li>
                </ul>
                <p>This plugin streamlines the process of adding documentation to your code with minimal effort.</p>
            ]]>
        </description>
        <change-notes>
            <![CDATA[
                <h3>🚀 Added</h3>
                <ul>
                  <li>Added <strong>keyboard shortcuts</strong> for quick comment generation:
                    <ul>
                      <li><strong>Project View:</strong>
                        <ul>
                          <li>Windows/Linux: <code>Ctrl + Shift + Alt + G</code></li>
                          <li>macOS: <code>⌘ + Shift + ⌥ + G</code></li>
                        </ul>
                      </li>
                      <li><strong>Editor View:</strong>
                        <ul>
                          <li>Windows/Linux: <code>Ctrl + Shift + G</code></li>
                          <li>macOS: <code>⌘ + Shift + G</code></li>
                        </ul>
                      </li>
                    </ul>
                  </li>
                </ul>

                <h3>♻️ Optimized</h3>
                <ul>
                  <li><strong>Optimized class comment generation logic</strong> to exclude method and field comments when building class text.
                    <ul>
                      <li>This reduces word count sent to the API, improving performance and reducing token usage.</li>
                    </ul>
                  </li>
                </ul>

                <h3>🐞 Fixed</h3>
                <ul>
                  <li>Fixed issue in <strong>Java file comment generator</strong> that added multiple comments to the same fields and methods.</li>
                  <li>Fixed issue in <strong>Kotlin comment generator</strong> where comments were being generated for local variables and functions inside methods.</li>
                </ul>

            ]]>
        </change-notes>
        <vendor email="info@countrydelight.in" url="https://countrydelight.in/">Country Delight
        </vendor>
    </plugin>

    <!--  test cases generator -->
    <plugin id="com.cd.test_cases_generator"
        url="https://github.com/cdcountrydelight/Plugin-Manager/raw/refs/heads/master/test_cases_generator-1.0.2.zip"
        version="1.0.2">
        <idea-version since-build="241" until-build="251.*" />
        <name>Test Cases Generator</name>
        <description>
            <![CDATA[
               Effortlessly generate unit test cases for Kotlin functions with this plugin. It analyzes function
        parameters, return types, and behavior to create well-structured test cases, ensuring comprehensive coverage.
        Supports functions inside classes, objects, and standalone files while preventing duplicate test generation.
            ]]>
        </description>
        <change-notes>
            <![CDATA[
                <ul>
                    <li><strong>Added support for Kotlin K2 mode</strong>, ensuring compatibility with the latest Kotlin analysis engine.</li>
                    <li><strong>Defined maximum supported IntelliJ version</strong> (<code>until-build</code>), ensuring proper compatibility across IDE versions.</li>
                </ul>
            ]]>
        </change-notes>
        <vendor email="info@countrydelight.in" url="https://countrydelight.in/">Country Delight
        </vendor>
    </plugin>
</plugins>